It wasn't at all unusual for the Wermacht and SS troops to use Soviet tanks, but it wasn't always systematic. Combat machines captured from the Red Army were immediately sent back to battle, usually without any special refurbishment or modernization. Only in 1943, battalions of refurbished T34s were attached to the 2nd and 3rd Armored SS divisions Reich and Totenkopf. Some of these machines were reinforced with side screens; others received special stationary turrets to accommodate quadrupled 20 mm AA guns.