Clarence Johns, the aircraft designer, designed the Lightning as a long-range two-engine escort fighter. However, this Lockheed aircraft was used as recon plane (the well-known French author and pilot Antoine de Saint-Exupery flew one of them), as night-time fighter and as a ground attack aircraft. It was armed with a cannon and four machineguns and could carry up to a 1,450 kg bomb-load and up to 12 missiles. Altogether 9,927 such aircraft were built; the Germans respectfully nicknamed it "Horned Devil".