A flamethrower-equipped tank designed by Australian engineers on the basis of classic infantry tank Matilda Mk II. At the end of 1941 25 such machines were equipped. A flamethrower nose-piece was installed in place of the cannon and a container with liquid incendiary mix was placed in the turret. The flamethrower was pneumatic; the pause between bursts was at least 20 seconds. This modification of the Matilda was used in New Guinea and proved to be quite efficient against the entrenched Japanese.