OPERATIONS ORDER 73-44

DATE December 1944

The roads that run alongside the lakeshore here are being used by Allied troops intent on moving south and capturing your current position.  Headquarters is reluctant to concede this strategic location and asks that you maintain control of your position in the face of the enemy attacks.  Once a sufficient defense is established, the next priority will be to move north, attack and occupy the current enemy position.  Despite the numerical superiority of the enemy forces, command has confidence in the capacity of your forces.

SIGNED: General Hasso von Manteuffel