A cannon designed for hitting targets deep inside enemy territory and destroying bunkers. Superior in firepower when compared to the German K18 cannon, but less accurate. В целом, с учетом высокой мобильности орудия, одна из лучших систем в своем классе. Широко применялась после войны в локальных конфликтах.

SPECIFICATION:

Caliber         -  114 mm
Rate of fire   -  2 shots/min
Range          -  18.7 km
Weight         -  5370 kg