OPERATIONS ORDER 34-41
DATE December 1941

A large German force is approaching this area from the north, and will certainly strike soon in an attempt to capture the nearby road.  Your responsibility will be to direct the defense that must stop the enemy progress.  There is a reportedly a lack of organization among our positions here, so you may have to rearrange troops quickly in order to make the most efficient use of the generous forces at your disposal here.
 
SIGNED: General Ivan Konev