Your fist priority here is to break through enemy defences and capture the town. This town is your main goal. While attacking the town please defend the township against Allied attacks from the north.  The enemy has a large amount of mobile armor and artillery and you can expect to receive extremely heavy fire.  Your own artillery will be your best defense, and should be able to keep the ground troops at bay.