The first torpedo-bomber, produced by the firm Grumman and resembling fighters of the same firm. An "Avenger" was notable for high durability and powerful defensive weapons. The distinctive feature, unusual for the single-engine aircraft, was the fully mechanized turret. Placing a torpedo on the internal bracket of the aircraft affected the flying abilities. "Avengers" scored hits  on a great number of Japanese ships, including the most high-powered battleships in the world "Yamato" and "Musasi".