As we maintain our advance, 7th Armored's reconnaissance teams have spotted a German vanguard unit in a cantonment within a small desert village to the east. This is apparently an attempt to build a springboard from which the Germans could harass Eighth Army's supply lines, or perhaps launch a counter-offensive into Egypt. Whatever its purpose, it is now yours for summary liquidation. The Jerries must not seize the initiative; or else our armored units may become severely bogged down here on the way to Tripoli.