The first serial armored tank destroyer in the world, called 4,7 cm Pak (t) auf Pz.Kpfw.l Ausf.B Panzerjaeger I. Designed by the firm Alkett after the operations had already begun. It was a Czech 47 mm AT cannon on the chassis of the light tank Pz I. First the tank "Panzerjaeger I" was used in France. It proved to be better than regular tanks in the fight with the enemy tanks. However, from the moment of the introduction into the USSR it already did not meet the requirements needed and was replaced by the more effective SPG.