OPERATIONS ORDER 56-40
DATE May 1940

The enemy is still retreating across the river at will here, and must be stopped. Your assignment is to lead the way across the river quickly using one of the three bridges in this area, and then establish strong points with your tanks that will prevent the enemy from further crossings.  A high speed of movement will be essential to your success here near the river.  Our armies are advancing across the map and the victory can not be far off now!

SIGNED: General Ewald von Kleist