OPERATIONS ORDER 29-42
DATE April, 1942

The prototype of the modern medium tank was damaged during the test run in the jungle. Even worse, the fast-moving enemy troops have cut off this tank from our positions. We do not leave our men and we do not allow the enemy to capture the precious equipment. The rescue mission is ordered to retrieve the tank and the crew, provide repairs and escort the unit to its new post.

SIGNED: General Douglas MacArthur