Brigadier Rodgers at Twelfth Corps reports that a detachment of armored reconnaissance troops have become separated from the main body of their unit, possibly becoming disoriented during the recent sandstorms. We are sending you into a potentially hostile area to try and lead these men to safety. There is no reliable intelligence on what you might find in this region. If confronted by the enemy your orders are to appraise the situation and take whatever actions are warranted in order to complete your rescue mission.