Listen up - I know the objective is to clear the Japs out of that strongpoint up ahead, but the first thing is obviously to defend our starting position. Do not let the enemy push us out. Then we'll launch a counter-attack. You can go up the middle and try overwhelming them with massive force, or you can try Captain Peterson's notion of going the long way around, and beating the outlying Japanese infantry posts along that road to the east. 