OPERATIONS ORDER 24-46
DATE October 1944

We've been doing well against the Japanese… up 'til now. Our forward elements have recaptured some pillboxes up ahead, and are squaring off with the Japanese for control of the roads in this sector. The Japs have been making useless infantry thrusts against our line, but their own line is too well fortified for us to risk a frontal attack. Captain Peterson had an idea to go on a whirlwind charge up the eastern road, turning the enemy's left flank and hitting them hard in their rear… what do you think?

SIGNED: General Walter Krueger