The minimap is located in the bottom left-hand corner of the screen and shows the entire game map. Green points show your units, while red points show enemy units that are visible. To use the minimap to navigate, left click inside it and hold the button down while moving the cursor to the part of the map you wish to display on the screen.
Move your tank further down the road to go to the next objective.