OPERATIONS ORDER 31-42
DATE July 1942

The Germans have recently seized the village to the northeast of our artillery battery here, and have begun to attack the battery directly now.  Your urgent assignment is to quickly assist in the defense of this artillery position, and ensure that this artillery unit continues to function.  Although the enemy has the numerical advantage, your tanks should give you the superior forces, and reinforcements will be available from our southern locations.  You may also use airborne fighters, against both the attackers and the enemy stronghold. 

SIGNED: General Ivan Petrov