<color=FFCFCFCF>Look at the button in the top right-hand corner of Button Panel. This command is "Hold Position". To set selected unit into the "Hold Position", state left click on this button. In the "Hold Position" state the unit doesn't move, even if enemy unit is detected within its field of view. However, it attacks target as it enters into the firing range.
 Set ALL your units into the "Hold Position" state and repell enemy attack.
Select the tank, then command it to Hold Position (<color=FFCFCF00>'R'<color=FFCFCFCF> key).