We are now ready to push into Libya, where we are soon to come into contact with Italian defence forces behind the border. Brigade intelligence has also detected an Italian column attempting to reinforce their front lines, but in all likelihood we will be able to hit and subdue their defence outposts before the reinforcements will arrive. Your orders are to slash forward and deal the Italians a humiliating defeat by destroying their units in detail. Do not allow the Italian groups to link up. 