Rocket Artillery
The recent advances of the military technology has led to the creation of this amazing weapon that is now available to you. It combines the mobility of the wheeled unit with the firepower comparable to the capability of a whole artillery battery. The rocket salvo that it can unleash within seconds wrecks havoc and instills utter terror in the enemy troops. If you can protect these rather vulnerable machines from enemy fire and move in a favorable position for firing, you may witness enemy heavy armor, fortifications and defenses alike turn into a charred and lifeless wasteland.