OPERATIONS ORDER 14-45
DATE April 1945

The enemy lines have been broken along the entire front here.  As the panicked German troops now rush westward in retreat, we have the ability to severely reduce their numbers.  In order to prevent these troops from being used against us as we march towards Berlin, your artillery must target these fleeing forces and eliminate as many as possible.  You can expect several waves of German infantry and light vehicles to come streaming past your position.  We wish you happy hunting and good shooting!

SIGNED: Marshal Georgy Zhukov