Greetings, commander. We are to prepare the battlefield for a surge forward by our armored forces, and eliminate the enemy anti-tank and artillery strongpoints prior to the commencement of the armored maneuver. Once this is complete, the armored boys will owe us champagne and crumpets. Let's practice our artillery accuracy. We have noticed several abandoned German anti-tank guns within our reach; I would strongly recommend turning these around against their former owners. With luck, we can clean the enemy off those roads in two hours.