The best medium tank of the war. Didn't have outstanding advantages by any single evaluation parameter, but the overall performance was much better than all foreign machines of the same class. Vehicles made in 1940 - 1941 had one serious drawback: the small cramped turret could only accommodate two crew members, and hampered the commander's actions in combat. At the beginning of the war many of the machines didn't have radios.