OPERATIONS ORDER 61-41
DATE December 1941

This important assignment involves directing the counterattack against a salient of stubborn invaders in the town of Klin. Many troops, and armored units are at your disposal.  To rout the enemy forces, you will need to first sweep west, penetrating enemy defenses as you work your way in a march that will yield the key bridges across the rivers.  Once you are able to move south, you will need to capture the town of Klin itself, and then finally take possession of the critical munitions factory.
 
SIGNED: General Ivan Konev