OPERATIONS ORDER 35-51
DATE December 1941

Although this area is mostly surrounded by snowfields, two different groups of German troops are taking advantage of the good roadway and rail bed here to make rapid progress towards the town and the critical munitions factory that sits to the east.  We are, of course, moving the key production equipment out of town via the railroad, and your assignment will be to keep the enemy at bay until the full shipment can be safely loaded on freight cars and removed to the south.

SIGNED: General Ivan Konev