The tank was named after St. Valentine: the design was presented to the War Ministry on the saint's day, February 14. Altogether 8,275 such tanks were supplied to British and Canadian armed forces, with different armaments and turret designs (11 various modifications). A large proportion of the total number of manufactured tanks (3,782) were shipped to the USSR. Both British and Soviet crews noted the Valentines' reliability and maneuverability, but by the end of the war it was no match for the heavy German tanks.