Designed in 1931, adopted by the army in 1932. The design was based on the captured 81 mm Stocks-Brandt mortar used by the armed forces of many countries. Compared with the prototype model, the frame was redesigned quite radically: it became two-wheeled, allowing both vertical and horizontal adjustment. In addition to the 1937 model there were also 1936, 1941 and 1943 models of this mortar, with minor modifications.