OPERATIONS ORDER 81-44
DATE December 1944

British forces in this area are not well prepared for defense, although more troops are arriving.  The river crossing deep in the enemy positions may be important for our further actions. Regional command has asked that you be given the assignment of directing the offensive action here. Break through enemy resistance and capture the bridgehead.

SIGNED: General Hasso von Manteuffel