An American military three-axis truck; unlike other America automobiles, it didn't have an I-head engine (as it should have done) but instead an L-head one, which didn't meet the US army requirements. That's why Studebaker US6 was supplied to the Allied armies, mainly to the USSR and Great Britain. The Red Army received 152,000 such vehicles; they gave an excellent account of themselves on the Soviet-German front.