As the German war machine falls further apart, their troops are retreating across the map and organising themselves into a bitter defense of their home territory.  Fortunately, our valiant troops are finding success in every effort, and we have no doubts that we may soon enjoy the pleasure of seeing Soviet troops become the masters of even the German capital.  But the enemy still has teeth to show, and the final push towards Berlin will not be easy.  Our heroic resolve can not be allowed to wane, and the glorious Russian banner must move ever forward towards our final victory! 