With surprise on our side for once, High Command has seen fit to strike at one of the main German airfields far behind enemy lines. We have crossed the desert wastes with little time for rest or repair, and have caught the German airfield with only a small covering force present. You must deal effectively with the defensive patrols and secure the airfield, seizing whatever documents you may find in the nearby buildings. Neutralizing the airfield will increase our own air superiority in the region. 