The Americans have captured a port city which we are now trying to reinforce by sea. However, von Kesselring has sent copious amounts of force against the American landing; it may be too late for us to make a difference, but we shall try. We have only the HMS Erebus and some naval air assets at our disposal; we shall endeavor to harass the Germans sufficiently to allow the Americans to hang onto the staging port.