Light and compact anti-tank cannon used against light and occasionally medium tanks at the beginning of the war.  Has a unique ring fire feature but cannot be moved by the crew when primed.  Highly inferior to the German Pak-38 50 mm cannon. Пушка полностью соотвтствовала периоду, когда легкие танки были весьма быстроходны, но слабобронированы. На момент своего появления была способна решать возлагавшиеся на нее задачи.

SPECIFICATIONS:

Caliber         -  40 mm
Rate of fire   -  15-20 shots/min
Range          -  2.3 km
Weight         -  600 kg