Our comrades are holding the defense line to the west of the lake. The intelligence indicates that the main enemy attack will come that way. Join your neighbors and hold off the enemy attacks. The Germans will throw very strong armor against you towards the end. You have the right to deploy Katushas, but use them as the last resort. If necessary, you must destroy them rather then let fall into enemy hands.