OPERATIONS ORDER 103-42
DATE April, 1942

More bad news. The Japanese have captured Singapore and have invaded the Phillipines in force. The good news is the Japanese aren't particularly well-versed in modern infantry tactics, nor is their equipment all that great. The bad news is their fanaticism and fighting spirit are unmatched, and we won't have good equipment either until we can be reinforced from the States. Your job is to organize the defense of the Bataan Peninsula near Manila until we evacuate our main forces… in other words, for as long as possible.

SIGNED: General Douglas MacArthur