<color=FFCECFCE>You must dig a few trenches between two pillboxes on the bridgehead. To do so you must use engineers.

Engineers can dig trenches. Select one of the trucks. Then click the <color=FFCFCF00>"Dig Trenches"<color=FFCECFCE> button. The buttons area will change. You can specify the point where you want the trench to start. Just click on the game map. A trench project will appear. The green squares shows that the area is free and the trench can be built there. Click at the point where you want the trench to end. The engineers will start working.