A 105 mm fire support SPG built on the basis of the M3 medium tank, with lightened body and open-top turret. Designed in 1942, the M7 was the first full-fledged SPG manufactured by Anglo-American allies. 90 machines of this type were immediately sent to the 8th British Army in North Africa (September, 1942), and took part in the battle of El Alamein. Altogether 4,316 M7s were manufactured until February, 1945.