A T34 equipped with 85 mm artillery system. There were two modifications of T34-85: one with 85 mm D5T cannon (the earlier version) and the other with 85 mm ZiS S53 cannon (the main model). The S53 could pierce 111 mm armor at 500 m, and 102 mm armor at 1,000 m. These capabilities allowed T34-85 to counter the German Pz.Kpfw.V Panther or Pz.Kpfw.IV Ausf. E Tiger. By the end of the war T34-85 became the core Red Army tank.