The only Soviet four-engine bomber made during the WW2. Altogether 79 such aircraft were built. In terms of flying properties the Pe8 was equal to all American and British bombers of the first period of the war. However, unlike the Allies the USSR didn't conduct systematic bombings of the enemy enterprises. That's why it was decided to discontinue production of Pe8 in favour of front-line bombers.