OPERATIONS ORDER 53-44
DATE December 1944

South of the river and the factory, we occupy a strategic position.  We ask you now to take command of the defenses of this location, and guard against any attacks from the forces that seem to be building up north of the river. Keeping German control of the bridges is one certain key to maintaining a solid defensive perimeter and not allowing the Allied forces to attack with their tanks. In addition you must attack and capture the enemy supply depot. Feel free to attack whenever you have troops to spare.

SIGNED: General Hasso von Manteuffel