The Royal Navy has begun an intensive preparatory bombardment of Landing Zone ''Mandrake'' along the western coast of Italy. You are to lead the landing forces ashore and establish a viable beachhead. Problem is, many of the forces earmarked for the landing have been recalled at the last moment, and the Germans are rushing backup troops into the area. I tried to convey my doubts that this mission should proceed to High Command, but it will not be postponed. You are responsible for delivering victory nonetheless.