OPERATIONS ORDER 13-42
DATE September 1942

Headquarters asks that you now lead the armed group that protects this shipment. Although there are no large concentrations of enemy troops left in this region, there is still good reason to assign armed cover to any supply convoys passing through, as small mobile groups will harass any of our trucks using these roads.  Nonetheless, the shipments must get through, so your force of infantry and armored tanks will need to sweep the roadway clean and watch for any attacks on the flank and rear.

SIGNED: General Friedrich Paulus