OPERATIONS ORDER 68-42
LOCATION: Sebastopol
DATE July 1942

The Germans are establishing dangerous defenses in the areas they have occupied on the peninsula, and they must not be allowed to settle there.  Two key positions in this specific zone are howitzer artillery battery along the shoreline and the route by which additional guns will arrive. Your mission will be to go ashore under cover of darkness intercept the additional guns arrival then make your way to the already established positions, from where you can destroy the enemy artillery.  You must move quietly to avoid alerting the large German stronghold further inshore.
SIGNED: General Ivan Petrov