<br><justified>German Army is about to turn the new page in the History of Warfare.  Having learned the bitter lessons of Great War, the new generation of German commanders are ready for the rematch. Well equipped and organized German troops will rely on the modern armored troops and the tactic of Lightning War - "Blitzkrieg". Facing the fight on two fronts and being outnumbered by the Allied counterparts, German troops must be quick and courageous to achieve the victory that would make great German generals of the past proud.  