OPERATIONS ORDER 86-45
DATE March 1945

We've captured a bridge across the Rhine River which is of enormous operational importance as the Allied Armies close in on Ruhr region. We're going to send you forward to build up a defense of this bridge while we get some engineers in there to check it out. The situation to the east and south of the bridge is unknown. We assume the Germans don't want us to remain in control of this bridge, but we have almost no information on German forces in your area. 

SIGNED: General George Patton