The steppe country surrounding Stalingrad has experienced heavy pressure from the German forces, and the enemy has occupied a great deal of territory in this region.  It is now the duty of all Russian soldiers to dedicate themselves to the difficult task of uprooting these entrenched enemy positions and thereby begin the task of slowly pushing the Germans backward.   The great work begins here, and all of your assignments are critical small steps in the great triumphant march we have ahead.  A flood of loyal Soviet comrades, shoulder to shoulder, will sweep the invaders from our homeland soil! 