A light tank destroyer. Designed by the Czech MBB company on Wermacht commission. The design was based on the Pz.Kpfw. 38 (t) light tank. Supplied to tank destroyer batteries in all Wermacht formations, and to SS troops. Thanks to its compact size and maneuverability, the Hetzer (Hunter) was perfect for ambushes and cover action. 2,584 such SPGs were made between April, 1944 and the end of the war.