A "multistory" three-level (counting by the turrets) American-made medium tank. Out of the total 6,258 machines made, about 1,400 were supplied to the USSR. For the first time went into battle in May, 1942 (battle for Kharkov). Despite their powerful 75 mm cannon positioned in the side sponson, Soviet tank crews called this tank "communal grave for seven" and were relieved to switch to other models.