An efficient anti-personnel weapon.  Weighs much less than cannons of similar caliber and is better for eliminating enemy infantry.  Comparable to American and Soviet mortars of the same caliber. Весьма мобильное оружие, пригодное к переноске силами расчета. В ряде случаев, в горах, на болотах и в лесах оказывало решающее влияние на исход боя.

SPECIFICATION:

Caliber         -  82 mm
Rate of fire   -  20 shots/min
Range          -  2.4 km
Weight         -  57 kg