In the middle of 1936, following General Mannstein's proposal, design work on an assault SPG to provide fire support to infantry started in Germany. The assault gun was equipped with a short-barrel 75 mm L/24 cannon. It was tested in combat in France, and proved its effectiveness. The drawbacks included low off-road capability and low cruising range. By May, 1941 370 StuG III were made, in A and B modifications.