OPERATIONS ORDER 20-42
DATE September 1942

Entirely too many men and too much materiel is arriving in Stalingrad via river transport, and the pressures of our attacks upon the city are considerably lessened by the enemy’s ability to re-supply themselves. Command has therefore asked that you take charge of the operation to shut down enemy shipping on the river.  Using both artillery and aerial strikes, sink anything at all that tries to cross in front of you and expect both anti-aircraft artillery and enemy fighters to oppose your efforts.

SIGNED: General Friedrich Paulus