In July, 1942, British forces in North Africa were forced to retreat into Egypt after yet another attack by the ''Desert Fox'', Field Marshal Erwin Rommel. As the combined Italian and German forces of the Afrika Korps pursued the retreating 8th Army during August, the British shook up their command structure and began work on a defensive line to keep the Axis forces from cutting the vital Lend-Lease route to the U.S.S.R. via the Suez Canal and the Persian Gulf.  For newly appointed Lieutenant General Bernard Montgomery, the impending battle will be a critical test.  