OPERATIONS ORDER 34-42
DATE June 1942

Although we have hurt them badly, the Allied garrison still has ample stores, and in order to increase pressure we need to reduce their supplies. Your assignment here is to lead a group of commandoes in an attack on two key storage depots.  Your team will arrive by landing craft under cover of darkness. Then delve into enemy territory and fullfil the main objective. We have some limited back up forces in case the mission will go wrong, but don't count on it too much.

SIGNED: Field Marshal Erwin Rommel