Monty's just handed us a tough nut to crack. The lynchpin of the German defence line in Italy seems to be the rugged monastery town of Monte Cassino, built upon a mountaintop. Many lives have been lost trying to claim this place for the Allies, and the Germans have turned this forbidding terrain into a fortress. There does not seem to be any option but to reduce the monastery and knock the Germans further up the Italian peninsula. Try not to lose too many men.