A deep modernisation of the LaGG3/La5FN family of fighters. Thanks to scrupulous weight and aerodynamic analysis hundreds of the aircraft's elements and components have been subjected to, La7 boasted much better ceiling and rate of climb than La5FN - and with no increase of the gross weight. LA7 could carry a 2,100 kg bomb-load. I.N. Kozhedub, three times the winner of the Hero of the Soviet Union award, flew one of these planes.