A heavy SPG incorporating the chassis of the Tiger tank designed by Ferdinand Porsche and rejected by the military (the Nibelungen company built about 90 such machines before the results of the tender were announced). That's why the SPG was originally called the Ferdinand. In 1944, as a standardization measure, the Sd.Kfz.184 was renamed into Elephant. It was used at the Kursk Arc, in the Ukraine, Italy (1944) and Berlin (1945).