<color=FFCECFCE>While in mission you can call for reinforcements. Click the <color=FFCFCF00>"Toggle Reinforcement Mode"<color=FFCECFCE> tab at the top of the buttons block. Buttons block will change. To select the preferred reinforcement type click the appropriate button. The information about the reinforcement type will be displayed in the multifunctional area. To call selected reinforcement click the <color=FFCFCF00>"Call Reinforcement"<color=FFCECFCE> button in the bottom right corner of the multifunctional area. A marker on the minimap will point at the arriving troops.