Designed for hitting targets deep inside enemy territory and destroying bunkers.  More accurate than similar enemy weapons, but inferior to the Soviet A-19 122 mm cannon in terms of firepower and range and less firepower than the British 114 mm cannon. Более мобильна, по сравнению с советской системой.

SPECIFICATION:

Caliber         -  105 mm
Rate of fire   -  6 shots/min
Range          -  19 km
Weight         -  5640 kg