It always astounds me how easily we permit ourselves to lose the initiative after we launch an offensive. As we wait for Thirtieth Corps to forward more tanks, troops, and petrol to the battle area, we must closely guard the two bridges in our zone, even as airborne landings are still being made to the north. The Germans are somewhat disrupted by now, and though many of them have been cut off from higher command, even an idiot knows to deprive us of our bridges.