We have set you in charge of a mixed bag of units attempting to fight off various German units sent to evict us from a Dutch town we've taken during the advance. This happens to be the headquarters of Guards Armored Division, which of course is organizing the movements of its armored elements many kilometers to the north. Trouble is, the Jerries are bringing up their armor here, forcing us to rely on whoever we can get to form a barricade.