OPERATIONS ORDER 24-52
DATE October 1944

We've received new orders. Your part of the new operation will revolve around the capture of the Japanese seaport to extend our range of operations. This will be a joint Army-Navy maneuver… with all of the organizational headaches that entails. You'll need to sweep aside the Japanese naval covering force guarding the bay, and take the port inside. Plan your attack with that goal in mind.

SIGNED: General Walter Krueger