OPERATIONS ORDER 46-42
DATE June 1942

Equipment is precious here in this distant desert, and we cannot afford to lose any armaments casually. Unfortunately, at this moment we have a battery of anti aircraft artillery in a rocky area currently surrounded by enemy troops who are threatening to take control of them.  We need you to fight your way into the position with your tanks, and then use towing vehicles to haul the guns back out to safety without letting the enemy capture or destroy the equipment. 
  
SIGNED: Field Marshal Erwin Rommel