An integrated machinegun (handheld/heavy, depending on the supports) designed by Grossfuss company. Adopted by the military at the beginning of 1942. Its main strength was inexpensive manufacturing technology which still ensured the weapon met sufficiently high requirements. Was commissioned separately by the Wermacht (414,964 units made), the Luftwaffe (4,014 units made), Kriegsmarine (2,402 units made) and the SS troops (225 units made). 