<color=FFCFCFCF>While in mission you can call for reinforcements. Click the <color=FFCFCF00>"Toggle Reinforcement Panel"<color=FFCFCFCF> button at the top of the action buttons panel or press <color=FFCFCF00>'I'<color=FFCFCFCF> key. To select the preferred reinforcement type click the appropriate button. The information about the composition of the reinforcement will be displayed in the multifunctional area. To call the selected reinforcement click on terrain or minimap where reinforcement will head after deploying. A marker on the minimap will point at the arriving troops.