OPERATIONS ORDER 47-42
DATE September 1942

Access to the key village in this area is blocked by two very strong enemy fortifications.  We ask that you lead the effort to penetrate these defenses and get your forces in position to storm the town. Although destroying the fortifications completely is beyond your armors' capacity, your tanks should be able to engage the enemy in a covering battle.  Effective use of the sniper already in position should allow you to bypass the fortifications and slip your forces inside the enemy perimeter.

SIGNED: General Friedrich Paulus