OPERATIONS ORDER 75-40
DATE May 1940

This village ahead of you is the latest in the series of enemy strongholds that we need you to clear.  The road to your west is full of Allied reinforcements arriving to help in defending the town, so you'll need to capture the strategic building along that road to shut off those new arrivals before mounting a final push against the enemy headquarters and town itself.

SIGNED: General Heinz Guderian