The propaganda symbol of the Red Army's strike power, designed to break through fortified enemy defences. Made from 1935 to 1939 in small series, 5 -6 machines in each, noticeably different from each other. Altogether Kharkov Steam Engine Factory made 61 T35 tanks. By the beginning of the war 59 of these machines were attached to the 8th Mechanised Corps of the Special Kiev District, later transformed into the South-Western Front. All of them were lost in June - July; only two tanks have been actually destroyed in battle, all others were lost due to mechanical faults.