Designed under supervision of V.G. Grabin in 1941. However, after making 371 artillery systems of this type the production was stopped, "due to excess firepower and lack of appropriate targets". In 1943 the production of ZiS2 was resumed, after the system has been brought in line with the divisional ZiS3. These artillery pieces were used in antitank fighter battalions of rifle divisions, and GHQR antitank fighter brigades. Altogether 13,339 cannons of this type were made, of all modifications.