OPERATIONS ORDER 51-45
DATE March 1945

As preparations for the final attack in the Ruhr continue, Army Intelligence has handed us a high-priority mission: Colonel Nathan McCafferty, the Third Army's senior operations officer, has been shot down behind enemy lines. Being the liaison between Third Army and the Allied air forces, McCafferty knows almost everything there is to know about the planned attack. General Patton has directed that we rescue this officer before German Intelligence gets their hands on him. 

SIGNED: General George Patton