Americans designed this tank based on the actual combat experience in Europe, but despite a large number of weapons it wasn't especially popular with the crews. The main 75 mm cannon positioned in the side sponson had a limited arc of fire. The tank was equipped with four various engines (one model - with five Chrysler car engines - was nicknamed "egg-beater"). Altogether 6,258 such machines were manufactured in 1941 - 1942. The Americans used less than a third of them, mostly for training purposes.