The only aircraft designed by Junkers and manufactured while the designer was still alive (in 1931), which took part in the war. Originally designed as civilian airliner, but then was used as a military transport aircraft and even as a bomber. The three-engine Ju52 gave an excellent account of itself both in combat and on transport routes. As a bomber, the aircraft could carry 2,000 kg bomb-load. Altogether 4,850 Ju52 planes were made, of all modifications. "Auntie" was the affectionate nickname Wermacht infantrymen gave to the aircraft.