Major new technological advances were being made in the thirties, prompting many countries to design next generation aircraft to replace the old wooden bi-plane models.   The British Hurricane, Russian I-16 and Italian Machi were all considered benchmarks of the time with a monoplane design wrapped in a streamlined metallic skin.  It was the Bf-109, however, that truly embodied the idea of "next-generation" with a revolutionary design that incorporated nearly all of the advances in aircraft technology that had been made up to that time.  