A German bomber used by the Luftwaffe for 10 years; for 6 of them, the plane fought all over Europe and Africa - wherever the fierce combat was. The first flight of the aircraft's civilian version took place in 1935; the military version was manufactured since 1936. In its time it was the best bomber in the world. In the middle of 1944 production of the He111 model was discontinued. Altogether 5,600 such bombers were made.