OPERATIONS ORDER 64-42
DATE June 1942

All preparations are in place, and the attack against the enemy positions in this area will commence soon.  But in order for the attack to have a good chance of success, two critical actions must be taken beforehand.  First, capture the key settlement guarding the critical roadways in the area. And second, the enemy long range artillery to the west must be eliminated before our general attack begins. The battery is not properly set up yet, so we must act quickly. 

SIGNED: Field Marshal Erwin Rommel