Better armor and engine than the M3.  Highly maneuverable with decent armor.  Weaponry capable of countering enemy light tanks and personnel effectively, but the high silhouette made it rather vulnerable.  Inferior to the German Pz.III Ausf.J. Достоинства и проблемы М5 примерно те же, что у его предшественника М3 Стюарт. Но защита этого танка стала несколько лучше, также как условия работы экипажа и приборы наблюдения.

SPECIFICATION:

Armament primary          -  37 mm/L 53 /Q 123
Armament secondary       -  3x7.62 mm/Q 6250
Weight                            -  15 t
Max Speed                      -  58 km/h
Engine power                  -  220 hp
Crew                              -  4
Armor min/max               -  12/48 mm