Another moment of decision has come in the war against Nazi Germany. General Eisenhower has ordered Operation Market-Garden to commence. Monty's plan for this endeavor involves dropping our airborne units upon key bridges along a line of advance northeastward into Holland. This is the ''Market'' phase of the operation, which will be supported by the ''Garden'' advance by Thirtieth Corps, which will connect the bridges, and establish a clear land route not just into Holland, but into the heart of the German Reich as well.