A modification of the legendary child of British aircraft designer Reginald Mitchell. Spitfire V was designed as high-altitude AA fighter, so the plane's range was short. In May, 1941 the 41st, 54th, 64th and 91st RAF squadrons were been equipped with these machines, and only after the first combat flights of the aircraft was it presented to the public. The Spitfire V was better than its main competitor Bf-109F in terms of speed and maneuverability at high altitude.