A reconnaissance wheel-based automobile designed in 1939 by the White company. Technologically advanced, reliable, easy to handle, to the maximum possible extent standardised with half-track APCs of the M2-M9 family. Altogether 20,918 Scouts were manufactured until the end of 1944, including 16,438 of the new M3A1 modification (with a more powerful engine and compact cabin). The Red Army received 3,340 such armored vehicles.