A "V-2" was the first ballistic missile, adopted in the world. It was designed by the German engineers in the framework of "super-weapon"  development. A "V-2" was used mostly for bombardment of London. It turned out to be absolutely impossible to intercept the missile. There was no defense from it. But the absence of the specialized parts, low accuracy and high price (a V-2 cost as much as 5 fighters) did not allow it to greatly influence greatly on the course of the war.The "V-2" was used as a basis for the development of the post-war ballistic missiles in the USA, the USSR, Great Britain and France.