OPERATIONS ORDER 67-44
DATE December 1944

This mountain town in the Ardennes hangs on the edge of a cliff, and each street rises to a new level making the town into a series of roadway corridors where almost every building is occupied by Allied troops and tanks roam the streets.  German command has asked that we assign you the task of clearing this township street by street until a final attack can be mounted in which the enemy headquarters at the far north eastern edge of town can be destroyed. 

SIGNED: General Hasso von Manteuffel