The best German tank of the war. Designed by MAN company after the Soviet T34 model. Had armor plates positioned at rational tilt angles and was armed with a powerful 75 mm cannon (length of barrel 70 calibers). But despite the firepower the tank proved to be difficult to manufacture and maintain. It was practically impossible to repair Panthers in field conditions. The Pz. Kpfw. V fought in all theatres of operations except North Africa. Altogether, from January, 1943 to April, 1945 5,726 Panthers were made in Germany, of all modifications and functions.