The 76.2 AT gun which is sometimes incorrectly called a 77 mm cannon. According to British tradition, it was designated by the shell weight (17 pound). Design work started in April, 1941; the baptism of fire took place on March 6, 1943 in North Africa. The strengths include high armor-piercing capability (130 mm at 915 m and 192 mm at 500 m), and high rate of fire (10 shots per minute). The main drawback is the artillery system's large weight.