Work on this artillery system started soon after WW1. The French GPF cannon was taken as the basis (the barrel was actually incorporated in the new design without any changes). The American gun manufactured at the end of the thirties had two-axis carriage and telescopic supports. The cannon was nicknamed Long Tom for its long 45 caliber barrel; this nickname was passed over to the M40 SPG. The artillery system fought from July, 1944; its biggest drawback was low mobility.