An exceptionally successful tank, designed for infantry support. Unlike "Matilda" it had higher speed but less heavy armor. Due to the armor it was more effective than German light tanks, but was inferior to them in speed. During the war it was modified more than once, mainly weapons. Beginning with the Mk VIII "Valentine", it obtained a 6 pdr cannon, although being deprived of the machine-gun. The Mk X was equipped with a machine-gun again, and beginning with Mk XI a high-powered 75 mm cannon was installed on the tank. The powerful main gun was what made this tank the most efficient of WWII light tanks.