Army Intelligence believes that Afrika Korps is probing this area in order to find an escape route from El Alamein. We have placed you in command of an ad-hoc armored brigade with the task of blocking a panzer assault upon Bir Shahaab, and then seizing the settlement of Balad Aziza. The burden you must shoulder is immense - you will be up against Rommel's most seasoned tank veterans, possibly the entire 15th Panzer Division. Past experience with this lot has been memorable, to say the least.