As Nazi troops penetrate closer to the capital, our locally stationed troops must bend strategically, and establish new strong points that will block the enemy progress.   Stalling defenses, clever counter attacks, and the timely relocation of critical assets will all be a part of this heroic defense.  The audacity and sheer stupidity of the enemy attacks will become apparent as the sturdy Russian troops will prove too strong to defeat on their home ground.  In the defense of Moscow, the inspired Soviet troops will fight with their backs to the most important city in Russia, a prize worth defending with their last breaths.   