OPERATIONS ORDER 36-44
DATE December 1944

The Allied forces are pushing hard here and all of our positions are experiencing pressure.  Although there are no groups of hostile forces on the ground, enemy bombers and paratroopers are arriving frequently during the night.  These units are causing constant trouble for the defenders in the key positions we occupy, so your assignment will be to protect the fuel depots and most important buildings in the three townships here against these Allied air attacks.

SIGNED: General Hasso von Manteuffel