Hayabusa Ki43 fighter (Type 1, the Allied designation Oscar) was the most advanced aircraft in the Japanese army at the beginning of the war, but compared with the Allied fighters (P40, Hurricane, Spitfire) it was hopelessly obsolete. The later upgrades never got cannons, and the aircraft's speed in 1944 was no more than 580 kmph. However, the Hayabusa was one of the most widely used Japanese aircraft (5,919 planes manufactured altogether).