A high-speed tank which could move on wheels or tracks. Was made with cylindrical or conical turrets; there were modifications with petrol or Diesel engines (the radio-equipped core model, BT7M). Used in Khasan and Khalkhin-Gol (1938 - 1939) and during the war with Finland (1939 - 1940). At the beginning of the Great Patriotic war was one of the core tanks of the Soviet mechanised Corps. For the last time BT7 were used in august, 1945 - to crash the Guangdong army.