Anti-Tank Artillery
These weapons, small in size and uninspiring in appearance, can become a deadly threat to enemy armor when properly employed. Easy to move and fast to traverse, they are ready to face the enemy anywhere they go. Digging in gives the guns further protection that it needs to withstand the pounding that their mighty adversaries may deliver. The lack of any fortification may leave the guns exposed to the attacks of fast moving armor units or close contact with enemy infantry.