Field Artillery
Called by some the God of War, long range artillery is famous for giving the enemy hell on earth, while staying miles away in complete safety. There is nothing more breathtaking then a artillery battery delivering its devastating blow on the unsuspecting enemy positions. It's been a commonplace tactic to begin any major offensive with thorough artillery preparation. Their great range puts the guns well back from contact with the enemy's main forces, but an occasional raider, a surprise air strike or retaliation from the enemy's own long-range guns are the greatest hazards your artillery may face.